<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Virtual Farmers Market</string>
    <string name="title_section1">List View</string>
    <string name="title_section2">Map View</string>
    <string name="title_section3">My Profile</string>
    <string name="title_section4">Sell an Item</string>
    <string name="title_section5">Become a Seller</string>
    
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="action_example"></string>
    <string name="action_logout">Log Out</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_dialog_text">
		Bacon ipsum dolor amet andouille spare ribs chuck, leberkas swine rump ham hock turducken hamburger tri-tip ground round drumstick ham. Beef ribs bresaola swine, pork loin jerky turducken boudin tail. Cupim spare ribs doner shoulder biltong. Alcatra biltong leberkas pastrami, venison prosciutto meatball t-bone tongue kevin pig pork loin drumstick. Cupim salami pork belly bacon, turkey cow flank tri-tip capicola landjaeger ball tip ham sirloin jowl filet mignon. Turkey shank short loin filet mignon.
		\n\n
		Chicken meatball beef, biltong bresaola picanha turducken porchetta filet mignon boudin tri-tip. Sirloin strip steak chuck, bacon drumstick meatloaf hamburger rump pork belly shankle. Turducken doner jowl ham kielbasa short loin sirloin. Ham picanha ball tip filet mignon capicola fatback andouille. Chicken ribeye tri-tip brisket, fatback shankle rump tail. Bacon salami beef ribs, venison kevin ribeye pork loin tongue pastrami filet mignon pig strip steak.
		\n\n
		Flank hamburger pork chop, alcatra kevin ball tip beef fatback brisket pork belly pancetta. Alcatra fatback corned beef ground round, beef leberkas landjaeger turkey picanha hamburger rump. Pork chop short loin boudin beef sirloin. Venison pig leberkas, sausage jerky ball tip spare ribs meatloaf strip steak. Capicola beef ribs bresaola sirloin filet mignon strip steak frankfurter cupim. Biltong meatloaf pork chop strip steak brisket venison.
		\n\n
		Brisket kevin kielbasa beef. Spare ribs strip steak chicken pork belly capicola cupim short ribs. Ham hock porchetta landjaeger, cupim chicken pork chop flank cow bresaola spare ribs jowl short ribs turducken. Tri-tip pork loin shoulder bacon t-bone filet mignon ground round pork jowl rump tenderloin picanha pork chop. Hamburger alcatra doner pork loin tail jerky swine filet mignon ham andouille prosciutto drumstick brisket picanha pork. Strip steak jerky andouille capicola.
		\n\n
		Jerky beef ribs ribeye, ball tip pig filet mignon pork. Andouille pork shank ham spare ribs, beef beef ribs. Ribeye capicola tongue drumstick short ribs, fatback pig flank tail jerky short loin shankle andouille pork loin filet mignon. T-bone chicken ham shank shoulder. Picanha landjaeger swine doner chicken. Chicken leberkas tongue landjaeger sausage pork jowl venison biltong ribeye short ribs pork belly meatloaf kevin jerky.
    </string>

</resources>
